1.Why should we use functions at all?
- làm gọn code
- có khả năng tái sử dụng 
- dễ cập nhật
- phòng tránh lỗi thuộc về con người
2.How to define/declare a function?
The syntax for a function definition is:
	def NAME( PARAMETERS ):
		STATEMENTS

3.How to call/use a function?
*cách gọi function: gõ tên function kèm vs arguments của nó
 Name(arguments)
4. What is return, why and how do we use it?
-Return sẽ trả lại kết quả khi kết thúc 1 function
-nếu không có Return thì kết quả sinh ra trong function sẽ bị xóa khi func kết thúc

5.Do we have to use return in every function?
không phải function nào cũng phải dùng return

6.What are function arguments, why and how we use it?
*Most functions require arguments: the arguments provide for generalization

7.How to use function from a different file other than our currently working file?
* from tên file import tên hàm
vd: from ex7 import remove_dollar_sign

